<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
    <name>Eco plastic</name>
    <author>Lele</author>
    <packageId>lele.EcoPlastic</packageId>
    <description>**EcoPlastic Survival Frontier** transforms RimWorld with sustainable materials for your colony!

RECENT UPDATES:
0.0.0.65 Incendiary plastic tile: Extremely flammable for tactical construction/floor applications. Handle with care.
        
0.0.0.64 Incendiary Plastic: Bio-plastic infused with volatile compounds. Extremely flammable construction material for tactical applications. Handle with care.        
        
## 🌨️ **Designed for Extreme Climates**
Specifically designed for hostile biomes where wood, food are rares or nonexistent: arid deserts, frozen tundras, and Antarctic wastelands. Survive and thrive even in the harshest environments!

## 🌱 **Ecological Production**
Create bio-plastic at the biofuel refinery from common plant resources: agave, berries, corn, potatoes, and rice. Even greenhouse-grown crops work! No more dependence on traders for advanced materials!

## 🔧 **Five Specialized Materials**

**Plastic Basic** :
Entry-level material for basic furniture, structures, and recreation. Cheap and fast to produce.

**Plastic Industrial** :
Advanced version for high-quality construction. Greater durability and beauty for your premium structures.

**Plastic Bio-Steel** :
Advanced plastic bio-engineered steel created by reinforcing plant-based polymers with metallic compounds (Fabrication bench)

**Plastic Fiber** :
Synthetic textile for clothing. Sustainable alternative to cotton for dressing your colony.

**Incendiary Plastic**
Bio-plastic infused with volatile compounds. Extremely flammable construction material for tactical construction/floor applications. Handle with care.        
        
## ⚡ **Recipe for Biofuel Refinery**
- Recycle all plastics into chemfuel! Transform waste into energy for your generators.
- " Recycle " corpses of humans or animals into chemfuel!
- Convert hay to chemfuel

## **Traders**
Now traders bring raw resources: Plastic Basic, Plastic Industrial, Plastic Bio-Steel, Plastic Fiber, and Wood Planks

## 🎯 **Vanilla Friendly**
Perfect integration with the base game. Balanced for equilibrium gameplay without disrupting the RimWorld experience.

## ** Indoor crops **
Added Soil Basin and Tree Basin inspired by Hydroponic Basin
*Soil Basin*:
- 120% efficiency, no power required. Crop types: Corn, Cotton, Dandelion, Daylily, Devilstrand, Haygrass, Hops, Healroot, Potato, Psychoid, Rice, Rose, Smokeleaf, Strawberry, Tinctoria
*Tree Basin*:
- 80% efficiency, no power required. Crop types: Oak Tree, Cocoa Tree, Poplar Tree
Add Wall sun Lamp

## **Quality of life ( QoL ) **
Add light range indicators to all vanilla lamps: Wall Lamp, Flood Light, Standing Lamp, Torch Lamp, and Wall Torch Lamp
**Start your colony's green revolution today!**

Inspired by Plastic Revolution by Orbittwz.
https://github.com/orbittwz/PlasticRevolution

Completely rewritten implementation.
Licensed under MIT License.
Copyright (c) 2025 Emanuele Martinelli
https://github.com/GhChancellor/EcoPlastic</description>
    
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
</ModMetaData>
