<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
    <name>Eco plastic</name>
    <author>Lele</author>
    <packageId>lele.EcoPlastic</packageId>
    <description># EcoPlastic - English Mod Description

        **EcoPlastic** transforms RimWorld with sustainable materials for your colony!

        RECENT UPDATES:
        0.0.0.56
        - " Recycle " corpses of humans or animals into chemfuel!
        - Convert hay to chemfuel
        - Traders bring raw resources: Plastic Basic, Plastic Industrial, Plastic Bio-Steel, Plastic Fiber, and Wood Planks
        - Fix icon's color

        0.0.0.52
        - Plastic Bio-Steel (Fabrication bench) now available! Advanced bio-engineered steel alternative


        ## 🌨️ **Designed for Extreme Climates**
        Specifically designed for hostile biomes where wood is rare or nonexistent: arid deserts, frozen tundras, and Antarctic wastelands. Survive and thrive even in the harshest environments!

        ## 🌱 **Ecological Production**
        Create bio-plastic at the biofuel refinery from common plant resources: agave, berries, corn, potatoes, and rice. Even greenhouse-grown crops work! No more dependence on traders for advanced materials!

        ## 🔧 **Four Specialized Materials**

        **Plastic Basic** :
        Entry-level material for basic furniture, structures, and recreation. Cheap and fast to produce.

        **Plastic Industrial** :
        Advanced version for high-quality construction. Greater durability and beauty for your premium structures.

        **Plastic Bio-Steel** :
        Advanced plastic bio-engineered steel created by reinforcing plant-based polymers with metallic compounds (Fabrication bench)

        **Plastic Fiber** :
        Synthetic textile for clothing. Sustainable alternative to cotton for dressing your colony.

        ## ⚡ **Recipe for Biofuel Refinery**
        - Recycle all plastics into chemfuel! Transform waste into energy for your generators.
        - " Recycle " corpses of humans or animals into chemfuel!
        - Convert hay to chemfuel

        ## Traders ##
        Now traders bring raw resources: Plastic Basic, Plastic Industrial, Plastic Bio-Steel, Plastic Fiber, and Wood Planks

        ## 🎯 **Vanilla Friendly**
        Perfect integration with the base game. Balanced for equilibrium gameplay without disrupting the RimWorld experience.

        **Start your colony's green revolution today!**

        Inspired by Plastic Revolution by Orbittwz.
        https://github.com/orbittwz/PlasticRevolution

        Completely rewritten implementation.
        Licensed under MIT License.
        Copyright (c) 2025 Emanuele Martinelli
        https://github.com/GhChancellor/EcoPlastic
    </description>
    
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
</ModMetaData>
